Guide to the United Federation of Teachers Records WAG.022
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Officers and Staff Files
  - Subseries III:A: George Altomare Files.
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, 1964-1988 (Box 110, Folder 20)
    - AFT: Quest Conference, 1983-1985 (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - Annexes, Committee on: Report, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 22)
    - Announcements and Notices (UFT), 1961-1968 (Box 110, Folder 23)
    - Arricale, Frank, 1975-1978 (Box 110, Folder 24)
    - Art Teachers, 1973, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 25)
    - Art Teachers Committee, 1965-1967, undated (Box 110, Folder 26)
    - Art Teachers Association (NYC/NYS), 1983-1984 (Box 110, Folder 27)
    - Artists for Tax Equity, 1987-1988 (Box 110, Folder 28)
    - Artists for Tax Equity: Petitions, undated (Box 110, Folder 29)
    - Assembly Districts, undated (Box 110, Folder 30)
    - Assistant Principals: Supervisory Examinations, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 31)
    - Association of Chairmen in NYC Schools, 1967-1969 (Box 110, Folder 32)
    - Association of Classroom Teachers, 1963 (Box 110, Folder 33)
    - Association of Orthodox Jewish Teachers, 1967-1985 (Box 110, Folder 34)
    - Association of Teachers of the Deaf, 1962 (Box 110, Folder 35)
    - Association of Teachers of Social Studies of New York City (ATSS/UFT), 1963-1984 (Box 110, Folder 36)
    - ATSS: Conventions, 1972-1975 (Box 110, Folder 37)
    - Athletics Task Force, 1984 (Box 110, Folder 38)
    - Attendance, 1973-1983 (Box 110, Folder 39)
    - Attendance Teachers, 1962-1980 (Box 110, Folder 40)
    - Awards, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 41)
    - Bank Street School of Education: Symposium, 1969 (Box 110, Folder 42)
    - Berman, Herman E.: Councilman, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 43)
    - Bilingual Education, 1974-1984 (Box 110, Folder 44)
    - Bilingual Programs: Russian, 1971 (Box 110, Folder 45)
    - Biographical File, 1962-1992 (Box 110, Folder 46)
    - Black Heritage Committee, 1979-1984 (Box 110, Folder 47)
    - Board of Education: Action of Excellence, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 48)
    - Board of Education: Budget, High Schools, 1968-1985 (Box 110, Folder 49)
    - Board of Education: Budget, Statements, 1968-1985 (Box 110, Folder 50)
    - Board of Education: Budget Estimate for 1969-1970, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 51)
    - Board of Education: Bureau of Community Education, 1963-1965 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Board of Education: Calendars, 1985-1986 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Board of Education: Chancellor's Committee on Grade Organization, 1976-1977 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Board of Education: Circulars and Memos, 1956-1984 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Board of Education: Citywide Test Results, 1965-1967 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Board of Education: Columbia Association, 1968-1984 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Board of Education: Consultation Committee (UFT), 1960-1980 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Board of Education: Day School Organization Personnel, Report, 1960-1961 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Board of Education: Ethnic Distribution of Pupils in Public Schools of NYC, 1965 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Board of Education: Fiscal Consequences of 1975-1977 Agreement… (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Board of Education: High School Division, 1973-1981 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Board of Education: Newsletter, Bulletin, 1963-1983 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Board of Education: Personnel Committee, 1973-1985 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Board of Education: "Public Education in NYC: Reflections…A Budgetary Perspective", 1976 (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Board of Education: "Puerto Rican Profiles", 1964-1965 (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - Board of Education: "Staff Relations Plan for Professional Staff", 1956 (Box 111, Folder 16)
    - Board of Education: Standing Committees, 1977 (Box 111, Folder 17)
    - Board of Examiners, 1968-1985 (Box 111, Folder 18)
    - Borough Representatives, 1979-1984 (Box 111, Folder 19)
    - Boy Scouts, 1970-1984 (Box 111, Folder 20)
    - Boy Scouts: Relationships Committee, 1978-1983 (Box 111, Folder 21)
    - Brooklyn Domed Stadium Committee, 1984 (Box 111, Folder 22)
    - Brooklyn Education Task Force: Report, "The Failure of the Academic High School in NYC", 1970 (Box 111, Folder 23)
    - Brooklyn, It's Best in (IBIB), 1980-1981 (Box 111, Folder 24)
    - Bronx Education Endowment Fund (BEEF), 1985 (Box 111, Folder 25)
    - Brotherhood in Action, 1972-1973 (Box 111, Folder 26)
    - Budget: High Schools, Report, 1974-1981 (Box 111, Folder 27)
    - Budget Coalition for New York City Schools, 1970s (Box 111, Folder 28)
    - Cafeteria Service, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 29)
    - Career Education, 1977-1981 (Box 111, Folder 30)
    - Catholic Interracial Council of New York, 1979-1983 (Box 111, Folder 31)
    - Catholic Schools: Teachers, Organizing, 1966, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 32)
    - Catholic Teachers Association, 1977-1985 (Box 111, Folder 33)
    - Catholics in Education, 1975-1979 (Box 111, Folder 34)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Announcements and Notices, 1962-1987, undated (Box 111, Folder 35)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Lists, undated (Box 111, Folder 36)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Training, 1966-1984 (Box 111, Folder 37)
    - Children with Retarded Mental Development (CRMD) Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 111, Folder 38)
    - Chinese American Studies Committee, 1981-1984, undated (Box 111, Folder 39)
    - City University of New York (CUNY), 1969-1985 (Box 111, Folder 40)
    - City University of New York (CUNY): Professional Staff Congress, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 41)
    - Civil Defense Drills: Teacher Dismissal, 1962-1963 (Box 111, Folder 42)
    - Civil Rights, 1963-1967 (Box 111, Folder 43)
    - Civil Rights: Black History, 1975-1983 (Box 111, Folder 44)
    - Civil Rights: Freedom School Project, 1963-1965, undated (Box 111, Folder 45)
    - Civil Rights: Operation Reclaim, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Civil Rights: Selma, Alabama Pledge Drive, 1965 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Class Size Statistical Survey, 1961 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1963-1965 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Coaches Association, 1967-1981 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1960s, undated (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1961-1962 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1963 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1964-1965 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1966-1967 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1968-1969 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1971-1972 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1972 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1974-1977 (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1977-1978 (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1979-1980 (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1981-1983 (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1984-1985 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Collective Bargaining: Action to Support Negotiations, 1962-1964 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Collective Bargaining: Arbitration, 1972, 1985 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Collective Bargaining: Coalition of Municipal Unions, 1978-1980 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Collective Bargaining: Coverages, 1973-1978 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election, 1960-1961 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election, Eligible Voters, 1961 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election, Eligible Voters' Lists - Bronx Elementary Schools, 1961 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election, Eligible Voters' Lists - Bronx High Schools, 1961 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election, Eligible Voters' Lists -- Bronx Jr. High Schools, 1961 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election, Eligible Voters' Lists - Brooklyn Elementary Schools (P.S. 2K-P.S. 160), 1961 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election, Eligible Voters' Lists - Brooklyn Elementary Schools (P.S. 161-P.S. 614), 1961 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election, Eligible Voters' Lists - Brooklyn High Schools, 1961 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election, Eligible Voters' Lists -- Brooklyn Jr. High Schools, 1961 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election, Eligible Voters' Lists - Manhattan Elementary Schools, 1961 (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election, Eligible Voters' Lists - Manhattan High Schools, 1961 (Box 113, Folder 16)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election, Eligible Voters' Lists - Manhattan Jr. High Schools, 1961 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election, Eligible Voters' Lists - Misc., 1961 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election, Eligible Voters' Lists - Queens Elementary Schools, 1961 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election, Eligible Voters' Lists - Queens High Schools, 1961 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election, Eligible Voters' Lists - Queens Jr. High Schools, 1961 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Collective Bargaining: Election, Eligible Voters' Lists - Richmond, 1961 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Collective Bargaining: Elementary Schools, 1961-1963 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Collective Bargaining: Excessing, 1982-1983 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Collective Bargaining: Jr. High Schools, 1965-1967 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Collective Bargaining: Laboratory Assistants, 1963-1965 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Collective Bargaining: Library Media Committee, 1962, 1971 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Collective Bargaining: Music Teachers' Committee, 1965, 1971-1974 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Collective Bargaining: Negotiating Committee, 1963-1973 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Collective Bargaining: Paper, "How the New York City Teachers' Union Wins", 1964 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Collective Bargaining: Salary Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Collective Bargaining: Special Committee on Action to Support Negotiations, 1962 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Collective Bargaining: Strike Strategy Committee, 1962-1967 (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - Collective Bargaining: Strike Strategy, Rally, 1965 (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Collective Bargaining: Strike Strategy, Teachers' Vigil, 1963 (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - Collective Bargaining: Teachers of the Deaf, 1962 (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - College Bound Program, 1973-1981 (Box 114, Folder 21)
    - Columbus Day Parade, 1978-1979 (Box 114, Folder 22)
    - Committee for a Comprehensive Education Center (CCEC): Park East High School, 1966-1971 (Box 114, Folder 23)
    - Committee for a Comprehensive Education Center (CCEC): Park East High School, 1972-1975 (Box 114, Folder 24)
    - Committee for a Comprehensive Education Center (CCEC): Park East High School, Proposals and Reports, 1970-1973, undated (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Committee for a Comprehensive Education Center (CCEC): Park East High School, Sub-Committees, 1971-1973, undated (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Education and the Schools: Harlem Youth Opportunities, 1963 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Committee for an Educational Journal, 1963 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Committee of Interns and Residents, 1986-1987 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Committee on Middle East Studies, 1975 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Committee for the New York Institute of the Education of the Blind, undated (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1964-1984 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Political Education (COPE): Contributions, 1971-1984 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Committee on Political Education (COPE): NYSUT Instruction Booklet, 1982 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Committee on Political Education (COPE): Speaking Guides, 1974-1984 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Committee to Study Relations Between Executive Board and Negotiating Committee, 1963 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Committees, 1964-1973 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Communism, undated (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Community Council of Greater New York: Group Work and Recreation Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Community School Board, 1968-1979 (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - Community School Board: Elections, Endorsements, 1970-1977 (Box 115, Folder 17)
    - Community School Board: Lists, 1963 (Box 115, Folder 18)
    - Community School Board Districts, 1969, undated (Box 115, Folder 19)
    - Competency Based Teacher Education (CBTE), 1975-1979 (Box 115, Folder 20)
    - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA), 1973-1975 (Box 115, Folder 21)
    - Comprehensive High Schools, 1966-1974, undated (Box 115, Folder 22)
    - Conferences (UFT): Spring, 1959-1967 (Box 115, Folder 23)
    - Conferences (UFT): Spring, 1970-1985 (Box 115, Folder 24)
    - Consumers Union: Boycott/Strike, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 25)
    - Coordinator of Student Affairs, 1969-1973 (Box 115, Folder 26)
    - Coordinating Council on Education of the Disadvantaged (CCED), 1965-1966, undated (Box 115, Folder 27)
    - Coordinating Council on Education of the Disadvantaged (CCED): Sub-professional Vocational Education (SAVE), 1966, undated (Box 115, Folder 28)
    - Coordinating Council on Education of the Disadvantaged (CCED): SAVE, Manpower Development Training Program, 1966-1967 (Box 115, Folder 29)
    - Coordinating Council on Education of the Disadvantaged (CCED): Teacher Intern Education (TIE), 1965, undated (Box 115, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: Christmas Cards, 1975-1997 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: General, 1960 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: General, 1961 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: General, 1962 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: General, 1963 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: General, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: General, 1965 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: General, 1966 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: General, 1967 (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: General, 1968 (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: General, 1969 (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: General, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: General, 1971 (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: General, 1972 (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: General, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: General, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: General, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: General, 1976 (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: General, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: General, 1978 (Box 116, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: General, 1979 (Box 116, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: General, 1980 (Box 116, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: General, 1981 (Box 116, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: General, 1982 (Box 116, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: General, 1983 (Box 116, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: General, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: General, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: General, 1986-1988 (Box 116, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: General, undated (Box 116, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence: High School Committee, Chapter Chairmen, 1962-1964 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: High Schools, 1962-1974 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Memos, 1962-1985 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Memos, Daily, 1970-1971 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Memos, Daily, 1972 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Memos, Daily, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Memos, Daily, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Notes and Calls, 1964-1969 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Notes and Calls, 1965 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Notes and Calls, undated (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: UFT Members, 1960-1968 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Council for unity, 1977, 1984 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Cuomo, Mario, 1981-1985 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Curriculum Council, 1971, 1977, 1982-1983 (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Cyclical High Schools, 1976, undated (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Dean's Association of New York City, 1968 (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - Decentralization, 1966-1968, undated (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - Decentralization: Board of Regents Proposals, 1968 (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - Decentralization: Bundy Report, Responses, 1967-1968 (Box 117, Folder 19)
    - Decentralization: Report, "ESEA Title I Programs in NYC Schools", 1971 (Box 117, Folder 20)
    - Delegate Assembly, 1960-1984 (Box 117, Folder 21)
    - Delegate Assembly: Agenda, 1961-1972 (Box 117, Folder 22)
    - Delegate Assembly: Minutes, 1961-1966 (Box 117, Folder 23)
    - Delegate Assembly: Constitution, Petitions to Amend, 1968-1969 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Delegate Assembly: Correspondence, 1965-1979 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Demography of NYC School System Teaching Staff and Students, 1973-1975 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Desegregation/Integration, 1963-1965, undated (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - DiLorenzo, Jeannette, 1972-1979 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Disabled/Handicapped, 1965-1966 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Discrimination in Hiring, Dept. Of Health, Education and Welfare Charges, 1975-1979 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Discrimination in School System: General, undated (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Disruptive Students, 1962-1971, undated (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Disruptive Students: F.K. Lane High School, District 19, 1966-1967 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - District 1, Manhattan, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - District 1, Manhattan: School Board Meeting, Riot, 1968 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - District 2, Manhattan, 1972-1974 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - District 3, Manhattan, 1967-1969 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - District 4, Manhattan, 1966-1985 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - District 6, Manhattan, 1967-1985, undated (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - District 7, Bronx, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - District 10, Bronx, 1967-1983 (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - District 11, Bronx, 1967-1983 (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - District 12, Bronx, 1967-1967, 1982 (Box 118, Folder 20)
    - District 13, Brooklyn, 1967-1985 (Box 118, Folder 21)
    - District 14, Brooklyn, 1967-1985 (Box 118, Folder 22)
    - District 15, Brooklyn, 1981-1984 (Box 118, Folder 23)
    - District 16, Brooklyn, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 24)
    - District 17, Brooklyn, 1967-1984 (Box 118, Folder 25)
    - District 18, Brooklyn, 1967, undated (Box 118, Folder 26)
    - District 19, Brooklyn, 1967-1984 (Box 118, Folder 27)
    - District 20, Brooklyn, 1967-1977 (Box 118, Folder 28)
    - District 21, Brooklyn, 1967-1969 (Box 118, Folder 29)
    - District 22, Brooklyn, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 30)
    - District 24, Queens, 1968 (Box 118, Folder 31)
    - District 25, Queens, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 32)
    - District 26, Queens, 1967-1970 (Box 118, Folder 33)
    - District 27, Queens, 1967-1970 (Box 118, Folder 34)
    - District 28, Queens, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 35)
    - District 48, Queens, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 36)
    - District 30, Richmond, 1967-1977 (Box 118, Folder 37)
    - District Chairmen: Lists, 1974-1985 (Box 118, Folder 38)
    - District Representatives, 1969-1984 (Box 118, Folder 39)
    - Districts: General, 1963 (Box 118, Folder 40)
    - Driver's Education, 1980 (Box 118, Folder 41)
    - Drug Abuse and Prevention, 1971-1978 (Box 118, Folder 42)
    - Economic Development Council of NYC, 1969-1985, undated (Box 118, Folder 43)
    - Edmonds, Ronald R.: "Search for Effective Schools", 1977 (Box 118, Folder 44)
    - Education of Adolescents: National Panel Report, undated (Box 118, Folder 45)
    - Education Reform, 1974-1985 (Box 118, Folder 46)
    - Education Reform: "Political Myths About Reforming the Teaching Profession", 1984 (Box 118, Folder 47)
    - Educational Option Schools, 1979-1982 (Box 118, Folder 48)
    - Educational Park, 1965-1966 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Educational Park: Report, undated (Box 119, Folder 1a)
    - Educational Policies Committee, 1966-1985, undated (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Elections: Certificate of Literacy, 1957 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Elections: NYS Assembly, Altomare, 1966 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Elections (Non-UFT): Network Election Service, 1964 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Elections (UFT), 1962 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Elections (UFT), 1984-1985 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Elections (UFT): Announcements and Notices, 1965 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Elections (UFT): Ballots, 1967-1999 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Elections (UFT): Campaign Material, 1967-1983, undated (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Elections (UFT): New Action Coalition, 1981-1984 (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Elections (UFT): Nominating Committee, 1960 (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Elections (UFT): Results, 1964-1983, undated (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Elections (UFT): Vice President of High Schools, Arbitration, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Elections (UFT): Vice President of High Schools, Certification of Results, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 15)
    - Elections (UFT): Vice President of High Schools, Election Investigation Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 119, Folder 16)
    - Elections (UFT): Vice President of High Schools, Opposition's Exhibits, 1984-1985 (Box 119, Folder 17)
    - Elections (UFT): Vice President of High Schools, Petitions for George Altomare, 1963, 1967-1985 (Box 119, Folder 18)
    - Elementary School Committee, 1962-1969 (Box 119, Folder 19)
    - Environmental Science and Health, 1976 (Box 119, Folder 20)
    - Ethnic Studies, 1974-1976 (Box 119, Folder 21)
    - Ethnic Labor Coalition, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 22)
    - Evening High School Committee, 1963-1965, undated (Box 119, Folder 23)
    - Executive Board, 1960-1965 (Box 119, Folder 24)
    - Executive High School Internship Program (EHSIP), 1971-1981 (Box 119, Folder 25)
    - Executive High School Internship Program (EHSIP): Application, undated (Box 119, Folder 26)
    - Executive High School Internship Program (EHSIP): Grievances, 1974, 1979-1980 (Box 119, Folder 27)
    - Farm Laborers Organizing Committee (FLOC), 1983-1984 (Box 119, Folder 28)
    - Finance Committee, 1961-1963 (Box 119, Folder 29)
    - Finance Committee, 1978-1985 (Box 119, Folder 30)
    - Finance Committee: Auditors' Reports, 1963, 1975-1985 (Box 119, Folder 31)
    - Fiscal Crisis (NYC), 1971, 1974-1975 (Box 119, Folder 32)
    - Flexible Scheduling, 1969, undated (Box 119, Folder 33)
    - Ford Foundation: City High School Recognition Program, 1983 (Box 119, Folder 34)
    - Foreign Language Teachers, 1966, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 35)
    - Foreign Language Teachers, The NYC Association of, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 36)
    - Frontlash, 1971-1985 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Frontlash: Conferences, 1977-1985 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Frontlash: Labor History Course, 1972-1975 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Frontlash: Projects and Proposals, 1971-1981, undated (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Frontlash: Publications and Posters, 1972-1980, undated (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Frontlash: Reports, 1971-1980 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Frontlash: Student Logs, 1980-1985 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Funding: Proposal, Auxiliary Services for High Schools, 1976 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Funding: State and Federal, 1975-1977 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Funding: State and Federal, Correspondence, 1965-1977 (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Funding: State and Federal, Proposals, 1969-1977 (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Fundraising Committee, 1961, undated (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - Gay Teachers Association, 1971-1986, undated (Box 120, Folder 13)
    - Gifted and Talented, 1977-1982 (Box 120, Folder 14)
    - Golden, Carl, 1967-1972 (Box 120, Folder 15)
    - Gotthardt, Eleanor Goldenberg: District 19, Drama-Media Specialist, 1966-1988 (Box 120, Folder 16)
    - Government Employees Relations Report: Extracts, 1967-1968 (Box 120, Folder 17)
    - Greek Heritage, 1979, 1984 (Box 120, Folder 18)
    - Grievance Coordinator Committee, 1977-1980 (Box 120, Folder 19)
    - Grievances: Appeals, 1964-1965 (Box 120, Folder 20)
    - Grievances: Compensatory Time, 1973-1979, undated (Box 120, Folder 21)